I'm
Midnight in a plastic chair Breathing in the
stale dead air A broken cracker, a lukewarm
drink No time to rest, no time to think The
driver's waiting, knows my name A single piece
left in the game I feel the ache, a steady thromb
To what new hell have I become?
There's a fire burning on my skin A secret war
I'll never win I try to show her where it hurts She
answers back with silent smirks A roll of ice, a
heavy sigh Just another pressure, another lie
She doesn't see, she doesn't care Just leaves me
sitting, sitting there The clock is ticking on
the wall Before the final curtain calls I
planned the stops, I made the calls To get past
stations, halls and walls A world prepared to
help me through But what good does it do with you?
There's a fire burning on my skin Secret war I'll
never win I try to show her where it hurts She
answers back with silent smirks A roll of ice, a
heavy sigh Just another pressure, another lie
There's a fire burnin' on my skin A secret war
I'll never win I try to show her where it hurts She
answers back with silent smirks A roll of ice, a
heavy sigh Just another pressure Another life